Contact

7477055054 (Home) guptayash570@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/arpangupta-6836b5179 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Motion Design
After Effects
Motion Graphics

Certifications

Adobe Certified Associate in Graphic Design & Illustration Using Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Certified Associate Visual Effects & Motion Graphics Using Adobe After Effects

Honors-Awards

Best Attendance Award
Best Attendance Award

Arpan Gupta

Artist

Murwara

Summary

I have over 1 and a half years of experience working in Graphic Designing and Video Editing. Currently, I worked as VEDA's Graphic Designer for 2 months, improving skills by going on an internship for upcoming projects by using learned skills, creating and maintaining social media.

Showreel Links

Video Editing: https://youtu.be/W-m-W8xRaZA https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x4BFRewDRf4 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x914stiPEXU https://youtu.be/XFi1IIdY0Io

Motion Graphics: https://youtu.be/I9FW1aOImXI | https://youtu.be/rdaav3_R-jA | https://youtu.be/K_4Br__UQGM | https://youtu.be/F4xMNF0MFIY

VFX Roto: https://youtu.be/SjcsD8UiMjM

Experience

VEDA College (P.A. Inamdar College of Visual Effects, Design & Arts, Pune)
Graphic Designer
November 2020 - December 2020 (2 months)
Pune, Maharashtra, India

Jazbat Roohani Graphic Designer & Video Editer March 2020 - August 2020 (6 months) Katni, Madhya Pradesh, India

Robokalam Graphic Designer June 2020 - July 2020 (2 months)

Education

College of Visual Effects, Design & Art.

B.Sc MGA, Animation, Interactive Technology, Video Graphics and Special Effects · (2019 - 2022)

Kendriya Vidyalaya Ordnance Factory Katni 12 pass, Computer Science · (2018 - 2019)

Sacred Heart English Medium Senior Secondary School Katni 10, Science · (March 2016 - March 2017)